

Le Anh Tuan

Internship/Fresher Front-end Developer

Dia chi: Nga Tu So, Dong Da, Ha Noi E-Mail: letuanvn247@gmail.com

Phone: 039-420-9029 Facebook: fb.com/canopus247

Github: github.com/tenkaziol247

Summary

I'm a newbie web developer specializing in front-end development. I enjoy solving problems, finding solutions and interested in learning new technologies. I'm very passionate and dedicated to my task. If you feel my qualifications are a good fit for the position, I hope to have the opportunity to work with you in the future.

Education

06/2020 - 10/2020 CyberSoft - Programmer Training Center

- Basic Programming course: Thinking programming, Java language, algorithms, OOP.
- Front-end Foundation course: Front-end orientation, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, SASS/SCSS, Javascript (ES5/ES6), AJAX, JQuery, Git.

06/2014 - 12/2018 Vietnam National University of Forestry

- Bachelor of Forest Resources Management.
- Grade: Good.GPA: 2.99/4.
- · Full-time.

Experience

08/2020 - Present Personal Web Project

- Learning and practicing with many web projects.
- Build e-commerce, task manager, CV portfolio web projects.

02/2018 - 12/2019 Freelance Business

- Sale staff of Vinmart.
- Selling online on facebook platform.

Skills

HTML/CSS HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, SASS.

2014-04 VanillaJS, ES6, Axios, AJAX, RESTful API.

Typescript Syntax, Type, Interface, Enum,...

React basic, Hooks, Redux, React Route.

Nodejs Nodejs basic, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose.

Other libraries Material UI, Formik.

Git basic, Github.

Programming basic Comment, OOP, Data structure and Algorithms.

Soft skills Self study, teamwork.

MY PORTFOLIO

(02/2021 - Present)

Link	 Link demo: https://letuanvn247-portfolio.firebaseapp.com Link github: https://github.com/tenkaziol247/letuanvn247-portfolio
Description	The project presents my personal information and what projects have done.
Team size	
Position	Developer
Responsibility	Development.Fix bug, optimize code and maintain.
Technology	 Frontend: Reactjs, SASS, Formik, AOS, React Slick. Backend: Firebase. Deploy: Firebase.

TENJ TASK MANAGER

(01/2021 - 02/2021)

Link	• Link demo: https://tenj-task-manager.firebaseapp.com
	• Link github client side: https://github.com/tenkaziol247/tenj-task-manager-fe
	• Link github server side: https://github.com/tenkaziol247/tenj-task-manager-be
Description	Features like adding tasks, fixing tasks, deleting tasks, arranging tasks. Calendar displays tasks
	by day. Manage with personal account, update user information. The server side builds APIs
	and manages the data.
Team size	1
Position	Developer
Responsibility	Development.
	Fix bug, optimize code and maintain.
Technology	Frontend: Reactjs, Redux, React Router, Typescript, Formik, Moment, Material UI.
	Backend: Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, Jest.
	Deploy: Heroku, Firebase.

TENJ E-COMMERCE

(10/2020 - 11/2020)

Link	 Link demo: https://tenj-ecommerce-mui.web.app Link github: https://github.com/tenkaziol247/tenj-ecommerce-Mui
Description	Built-in shopping cart functionality, checkout, user authentication, account information, orders placed, list of products.
Team size	1
Position	Developer
Responsibility	Development.Fix bug, optimize code and maintain.
Technology	 Frontend: Reactjs, Redux, React Router, Material UI, SASS, Formik, Notistack. Backend: Firebase. Deploy: Firebase.